sonichits.com 2018-10-05

# None

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SonicHits collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the SonicHits.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by SonicHits.

## Personal identification information

When you register for an account, SonicHits only collects your email address and hashed password for the purpose of allowing you to sign in. You may alternatively visit our site anonymously.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## YouTube API

SonicHits uses YouTube API Services (see [Google's Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy) and [Youtube's Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms). SonicHits doesn't access, collect or store any YouTube user information, nor does it use, process or share any YouTube user information. The YouTube API is solely used to embed videos on the site, and in order to determine which video is the best to display (and offer alternative videos on our Videos tab, under the YouTube embed). 

## Lyrics

Usage of Lyrics is limited to your personal, noncommercial use in accordance with the terms of this Agreement. You may not reproduce (other than as authorized for your own personal usage), publish, transmit, distribute, publicly display, rent or lend, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in the sale of or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, directly or indirectly, any of the Lyrics so provided. You agree that you are not granted any so-called "karaoke" or "sing-along" rights to Lyrics and you shall not seek to or remove any vocal track from a sound recording that shall be associated with a Lyric provided to you. You agree not to assign, transfer or transmit any Lyrics to any third party. You agree that you shall not seek to or do anything that will defeat, evade or circumvent any efforts that may be made to protect the Lyrics from any unauthorized usage. 

## How we use collected information

SonicHits may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Updating and deleting your information

You can update your email address and password from your user preferences. You may also permanently delete your account by sending us a request to do so via email to support [at] sonichits.com. Your request will be actioned and all information permanently deleted within 3 business days. 

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

## Changes to this privacy policy

SonicHits has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please email us at: support [at] sonichits.com
